Sue: Hello, Pam. How are you this morning?
Pam: Hello, Sue.
I’m fine thanks, but you’ll never guess what’s happened.
Jack and Emma have broken up!
Sue: No! That can’t be true.
Jack and Emma? Your neighbours? I saw them last week and they looked really happy.
Pam: No, it’s definitely true.
I heard them shouting.
Hum, they were having a terrible argument.
Sue: No! When?
Pam: Last night.
After he came home from work.
Sue: What did they say?
Pam: Well, I wasn’t really listening…
Sue: Er, of course not.
Pam: But I couldn’t help hearing.
She was talking so loudly and of course the walls are very thin…
Sue: So, what did they say?
Pam: Well, she said that she was going to stay with her mum!
She told him that she wouldn’t come back.
Sue: Ooh, how awful. What about the children?
Pam: She said she’d taken them to her sister’s.
I suppose she’ll take them with her in the end.
And anyway, then five minutes later, I saw her leaving the house with a suitcase!
Sue: No! Why do you think she’s leaving him? Is he seeing somebody else?
Pam: Um, I don’t know…
Sue: I must go and tell Janet at number 14.
She’s always thought there was something…um,
something strange about him.